

Applicant for:

Senior Android Engineer ~2,000\$ (SL: 05)

Dr.JOY 12 April 2021

Tú Nguyễn

Main interests: Android, iOS

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Có nhiều năm kinh nghiệm trong làm ứng dụng mobile, có hiểu biết chuyên sâu về nhiều ngôn ngữ và nền tảng như Angular, Ionic, Android (Kotlin, Java), Flutter, React Native..

Ngoài ra còn có kinh nghiệm làm việc cường độ và áp lực cao ở nhiều vị trí khác nhau như Developer, Tester, PM. Có khả năng nhận và phân tích yêu cầu và triển khai yêu cầu đến đội phát triển. Có kiến thức, kinh nghiệm làm việc với nhiều kiến trúc khác nhau (MVC, MVP, MVVM, Clean Architecture, Bloc Architecture)



Profile

Experience with Android (+5 years) and Cross-Platform (Flutter, React-Native) (+3 years), in addition to understanding both Progressive-Web-App and Hybrid-App programming (Angular, Ionic).

Have advanced knowledge of Object-Oriented Programming

Have good knowledge of Java Core, Android

Ability to use **3rd party software** to enhance productivity (**Photoshop**, **Jira**, **Git**, **Postman**...)

Have knowledge of working with Agile Scrum

Ability to work in a team and work independently

Experience in leading and managing eams and projects

Ability to learn and impart knowledge to other members.

Understand English in IT

Employment History

Android Developer at Kloon Limitted, Hanoi

January 2012 - April 2015

Working and creating Android apps

- Ingenidoc / EFC / FunAlbum.fr: an app to buy and read PDF documents
- Arztsuche Osterreich: application to search and book doctor visits

Use RestfulAPI, Java, MVVM, GCM, Android binding

Proficient in interface design

Write custom components for special requirements

Understanding flow systems

Developer at Fruitful Technology, Hanoi

April 2015 - August 2018

Working and creating Android apps

- Prism: App/web to management horse racing
- Dorsal: application to notify shark-attack on Australia
- SilverTop Taxi: application to search and book taxi on Australia

Use RestfulAPI, Java, Architecture, GCM, Android, Firebase, ReactiveX, React Native

Proficient in interface design

Write custom components for special requirements

Understanding flow systems

Details

Hanoi

0396800550

tunt.program.04098@gmail.com

Date of birth

13-10-1990

Skills

SQL

Git

Android, Java, Kotlin

JS, HTML, CSS

Dart-Flutter

Angular, Ionic

Agile Scrum

Reactive Programing (Rx)

Research, solve problems

Languages

Vietnamese

English

Hobbies

Chinese chess, Badminton, Table soccer, CS GO, DOTA 2

Developer, Leader, PM at Bfast System, Hanoi

August 2018 - Present

Working and creating Android/iOS/Web apps

- ILW: Social networking application for French celebrities. Artists can post interactive, livestream or have their own personal page to provide products to fans (such as clothes, show tickets ..)
- Crous: Application to purchase products or services provided by a system for students / teachers in France. Use online payment services in France

Proficient in interface design

Write custom components for special requirements

Understanding flow systems

Education

FPT Aptech, Hanoi

September 2008 — April 2011

Higher Diploma in Software Engineering (HDSE) - Good graduation

HTML. CSS, JS, XML, SQL

Java (JSP, EHB, J2EE..)

.NET (C, C#, WCF, Win Form...)

Certificates

Higher Diploma in Software Engineering (HDSE))

November 2011 — Present

Agile Scrum

June 2016 - Present

■ References

Vu Manh Hai from Bfast System

0972734861